[{"answer": "I need you to come to this bachelor party for my weird cousin my friend, y'know he's the botanist", "docId": "312towj.htm.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "Yeah.  Is that a dinosaur tie", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "No, no, no, no turtles scare me.  I don't need that today", "docId": "312towj.htm.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "Oh honey, thank you, but my friend's taking me out", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "And who may I say is calling", "docId": "312towj.htm.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "my friend of....", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "This is my friend", "docId": "312towj.htm.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "Of my friend and my friend", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "my friend of....", "docId": "312towj.htm.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "Oh hi.  It's, it's my friend", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "Of my friend and my friend", "docId": "312towj.htm.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "Oh hey, hey my friend", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "Oh, he's just goofing around", "docId": "312towj.htm.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "Oh honey, this is his office too.  I told you we're my friend's two assistants", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "Ohhhhh yeah, that's, that's funny.  Why ah, why isn't he goofing around in his own office", "docId": "312towj.htm.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "Why does my friend need two assistants, how, how lazy is she", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "Look my friend, someone left their book here", "docId": "312towj.htm.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "Oh yeah, what are you reading", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "Oh yeah, what are you reading", "docId": "312towj.htm.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "Have I read it?   No, are you enjoying it", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "Hey, everybody lies on their resume, okay.  I wasn't one of the Zoom Kids either", "docId": "312towj.htm.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "Yeah, I can dance, y'know.", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "Why?!  How?!  How is he a genius", "docId": "312towj.htm.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "What am I going to do", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "All right that's, that's it!!  Get off her", "docId": "312towj.htm.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "What's going on?!   That's what's going on!", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "Yeah, it's a vase", "docId": "312towj.htm.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "Well not exactly like the one in the poem", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "So ah, did you have fun at the bachelor party last night", "docId": "312towj.htm.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "Right", "qsentId": 30}]